Well I'm gonna I'm
I'm being cheated on by my wife and she will never appear on this stream ever again.
And if you want to see her ever again, don't join this channel. Don't mention her
again, and we're done with this. I will never bring this up again. You can never
ever see it again. And that is it. Her Jordan is the person. If anyone wants to know.
And
This is now on the internet to 6,000 people. I wish you all the best of luck with
that. I'm never going to answer that again because it was the worst thing in the
entire world to have to say. However, whatever information comes out, just know this.
I am going to run this platform from now on 100% honestly. And if you ask me something,
I'm not going to fill your head with BS and absolute shit. I'm not. I'm gonna be
real with you.